streamica.com 2016-03-09

# 

## Privacy Policy

Streamica ("us", "we", or "our") recognizes that our users, visitors and others who use www.streamica.com website value their privacy.  
This page (this “Privacy Policy”) details important information of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use Streamica.  
The Privacy Policy only addresses our activities from our servers.   
Other websites, including those that we link to and third-party websites or services that we co-brand, may have their own policies, which we do not control, and thus are not addressed by this policy. 

### Information Collection And Use

We collect and receive information about you and your device when you give it to us directly, when you use Streamica, and from certain third-party sources, including Social Networks as login service providers. We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Streamica. By using the Streamica, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. 

### Log Data

We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit Streamica ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, platform type, browser type, referring pages and pages of Streamica that you visit, the date/time stump of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. 

### Cookies

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of the Streamica. 

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Streamica.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.streamica.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>. Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.streamica.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. Streamica.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.streamica.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

### Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

### Links To Other Sites

Streamica may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services. 

### Children's Privacy

Streamica does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children"). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we discover that a Children under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers immediately. 

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. Contact Us If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via contact form on [Streamica.com](http://www.streamica.com/). 

_Last updated: August 02, 2013_
